3dmailresults.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy - 3D Mail Results

———–

## SECTION 1 – WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling  
process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address  
and email address.

When you browse our site we also automatically receive your computer’s internet  
protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn  
about your browser and operating system.

Email marketing: With your permission, we may send you emails about our store,  
website, new products and other updates and news.

## SECTION 2 – CONSENT

How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify  
your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we  
imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we  
will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an  
opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my consent?

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to  
contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at  
anytime, by contacting us at [info@3DMailResults.com](mailto:info@3DMailResults.com) or mailing us at: 3D Mail  
Results 6205 S. 231st St. Kent, WA 98032

## SECTION 3 – DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if  
you violate our Terms of Service.

## SECTION 4 – 3D MAIL

Our store is hosted on Media Temple. They provide us with the hosting platform  
that allows us to sell our products and services to you.

Your data is stored through 3D Mail’s data storage, databases and via our  
Infusionsoft CRM. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

Payment:

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then 3D Mail  
stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data  
Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long  
as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your  
purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by  
the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa,  
MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by  
our store and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read 3D Mail’s Terms of Service here or  
Privacy Statement here.

## SECTION 5 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose  
your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they  
provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and  
other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to  
the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related  
transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can  
understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by  
these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities  
that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to  
proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service  
provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the  
jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a  
payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used  
in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States  
legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or  
application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s  
Terms of Service.

Links

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We  
are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to  
read their privacy statements.

## SECTION 6 – SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow  
industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused,  
accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted  
using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.  
Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100%  
secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally  
accepted industry standards.

## SECTION 7 – COOKIES

As you browse 3dmailresults.com advertising cookies will be placed on your  
computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display  
advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting  
advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with  
3dmailresults.com . The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal  
information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.  
You can visit this page to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

Customers can review, update or opt-out of future communications as well as  
correct their personal information by contacting us at 3dmailresults.com  
Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can  
choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

_session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows 3D Mail to store information about your  
session (referrer, landing page, etc).

_3dmailresults__visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit,  
Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits

_3dmailresults _uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the  
next day, Counts the number of visits by a single customer.

cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of  
your cart.

_secure_session_id, unique token, sessional

## SECTION 8 – AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your  
state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or  
province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your  
minor dependents to use this site.

## SECTION 9 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it  
frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their  
posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you  
here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect,  
how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be  
transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

## QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we  
have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our  
Privacy Compliance Officer at info @3D Mail.com or by mail at 3D Mail

[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]

[6205 S. 231st St. Kent, WA 98032]
